Now, I told you that Jasmine Crockett was a full of shit, Zionist climber.
And y'all said, stop bringing down black women.
I bring down black women who are bringing down black women.
Gotta be up and away.
And we've gotta make it.
Go out and vote again.
Do not get comfortable at all.
We are living in unprecedented times.
And I can tell you that there is no one better for this moment, for Missouri 1, to keep his eye on the prize, which is you, the people, than Wesley Bell.
Y'all believe me now?
Let me break this down for you.
Wesley Bell was running for a completely different office until the Jewish lobby, until the Israeli lobby, came to him and said,
We're gonna give you a bunch of money for you to run against Cori Bush, because we don't want her in Congress, because she is pro-Palestinian.
And so, because he's a coon, he did.
And it worked.
Cori Bush lost her seat in Congress.
When Wesley Bell announced his run against me, it was right after I introduced the Ceasefire Now legislation.
Wesley Bell said in his speech that he gave, he wasn't running against me because I wasn't doing my job.
He wasn't running against me because I wasn't turning out enough legislation, you know, because I was not on the job in some way.
Because he never called me to say, like, hey, sis, I wish you would do more.
I wish you would do better.
You know, never had that conversation.
So, because he stands 100% with Israel.
So he brought that into this.
Now, y'all know, I do not support electoral politics.
I think it's a bunch of BS.
However, this is about principle.
Cori Bush began as an organizer.
She had to be approached several times to run for office.
This was not a career decision that she made.
It was one that she eventually felt like was the next step in her being able to serve the people.
That's a very, very rare occurrence in politics.
She went into the position as a public servant.
She was ousted.
She is trying to come back.
And this Wesley Bell guy is still there and still funded and supported by the same folks who got her removed.
And Jasmine Crockett brought her BBL having, because, yes, she did get a BBL, having ass up there to stand and vouch for him.
Because they think you all are so dumb that if they just put a brown skin, neck waving person up there.
I'm not even going to go there.
You're going to vote for them.
They're using your identity against you.
They weaponized the very thing they have used to keep you down, to still keep you down by keeping you manipulated.
Jasmine Crockett is the shady lady at your job.
Jasmine Crockett is the conniving auntie.
Jasmine Crockett is the frenemy.
She is no different than people that are in your life.
So it is not about targeting Jasmine Crockett.
It's about targeting women and people who are willing to lie and manipulate in order to get themselves advancement.
Big up to Cori Bush.
And instead of being mad at me when I'm telling you the truth, don't believe the hype.